<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Intatera by Cheryl Marlene]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Intatera by Cheryl Marlene]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/intatera/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 13:52:54 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/intatera/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Failure and the Sexy Red Dress]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>As you may know, I have been going through divorce over the last year. A disconcerting process which bounces between deeply painful, wonderfully illuminating, and nearly unintelligible. Bounce is the operative word, like a ball thrown back and forth where sometimes you are the one bouncing the ball and sometimes you are the ball.I have concluded that my learning is this: Choice. However I be bounced, I definitely get a choice about how I am going to experience this ball toss. I may not be able to choose the outcome, but I do have a choice about my response.Last September, after a particular tiring back and forth, I seriously contemplated my choice. What do I want from divorce? I let my mind run wild, bouncing around all kinds of possibilities from the mystical (a trip to Shambala) to the mundane (a new sofa), from the unlikely (a sports car) to the unkind (a muzzle for you-know-who).I decided I wanted something that would have great personal meaning for me and me alone. I did not want to compromise and I wanted something obtainable. I wanted to be over-the-moon excited. I wanted a door to my future, rising up out of the ashes of my past. And it had to be red.One night, my choice came to me. Struck by the proverbial lightning bolt of deep realization, I knew what I wanted from this bouncing: a sexy red dress. Yep. A sexy red dress. No doubt. A sexy red dress. AND, I realized, if I am getting my sexy red dress, then I needed something else: the body to go in my sexy red dress.I confess I have struggled with my weight for a very long time, at least 20 years. By declaring the desire for the sexy red dress and by declaring my intention to have the body for the sexy red dress, I was picking something both very significant for me and something that had always been illusive and seemingly unobtainable.The sexy red dress was exactly what I wanted. This sexy red dress was my dream, the light at what was turning into a very long tunnel. Decision made, I committed to myself and to my sexy red dress. Come what may, I knew that I had to find a way to create my path towards this sexy red dress.I started telling friends about my decision. I started thinking about what kind of sexy red dress I wanted. My sexy red dress began to feel real and possible. For almost the first time in 20 years, I was losing weight and I was feeling better and better about myself with every bounce and with every encouragement and with every thought of my sexy red dress.I knew I was on the right track for myself. Out shopping with a friend, I asked should I buy these earrings? Her answer "Yes, they will be perfect with your sexy red dress!" Others started sending me pictures of sexy red dress possibilities, while others held back on cookie and cake offers. Everyone smiled with me, visualizing me in my sexy red dress. I began a vision board on a kitchen cabinet door, hanging sexy red dress pictures in clear view. I could feel my dress moving towards me, joining me in my new life, offering the very real possibility of dreams fulfilled.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/intatera/as-you-may-know-i-have-been-going-through-divorce-over-the/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">711ca47b-c589-4fa5-9773-466b23cd6aba</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 13:52:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>